genius-tips.com 2013-05-30

# Privacy Policy

At Genius-Tips.com we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important and we take your privacy very seriously. **We never sell your personal information to third parties.**

We use third party advertisements on Genius-Tips.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site. Google, through their Adsense Program, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Genius-Tips.com users based on their visit to this and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

Also we reserve rights to change or replace this Privacy Policy at any time without any prior notice. The information on this website is only for information purpose.
